怎么会有人知道你的信用卡号码?
How'd someone get a hold of your credit card number?
我也不知道 你看他们花了多少钱
I have no idea. But look how much they spent!
摩妮卡 冷静点
Monica, would you calm down?
信用卡的人说你只要付你所买的东西
The credit card people said that you only have to pay for the stuff that you bought.
但这真的是挥霍无度
Still, it's just such reckless spending.
我想他们偷你的信用卡时
I think when somebody steals your credit card
早就将王法抛诸脑后了
they've kind of already thrown caution to the wind.
哇 真是怪人 花了69.95元买"神奇拖把"
Wow, what a geek. They spent $69.95 on a Wonder Mop.
那是我买的
That's me.
噢 它又来了
Oh! Oh, the yuck.
他又来了
Ross, he's doing it again!
马赛尔 别再侵犯那盏灯了
Marcel, stop humping the lamp!
不要这样 马赛尔 回来!
Stop humping! Now, Marcel, come back!
过来这里 马赛尔
Come here, Marcel!
不要!别去我房间!我去抓他
Oh, no, no! Not in my room! I'll get him.
罗斯 你得想想办法
Ross, you've got to do something about the humping.
怎么了?这只是阶段性的而已
What? It's just a phase.
我们也是那样说乔伊的
Well, that's what we said about Joey.
放轻松点好吗? 没什么大不了的
Hey, would you all relax? It's not that big a deal.
马赛尔 停! 马赛尔! 坏猴子!
Marcel, stop it! Marcel! Bad monkey!
怎么了?
What? Ugh!
我只能说 我的好奇乔治娃娃已经不再好奇
Let's just say my Curious George doll is no longer curious.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第21集
假摩妮卡 The One With the Fake Monica
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：小龟快快跑 悠悠慕雪
摩妮卡 你不会还在看那个东西吧
Ugh, Monica, you are not still going over that thing.
这个女人在过着我的生活      什么?
This woman's living my life.        What?
她过着我的生活 而且过得比我好
She's living my life, and she's doing it better than me.
你看这个 看
Look at this. Look.
她买的票是我一直想看的戏剧
She buys tickets to plays I want to see.
她买的衣服是我早就想买的
She, she buys clothes from stores that I'm intimidated by the sales people.
她花三百刀买艺术用品
She spent three hundred dollars on art supplies.
你又不是艺术家
You're not an artist.
如果有艺术用品 我或许就已是艺术家了
Yeah, well, I might be if I had the supplies.
这些我都可以做 只是我都没做
I mean, I could do all this stuff. Only I don't.
摩妮卡 别这样 你有做很酷的事情啊
Oh, Monica, come on. You do cool things.
是吗? 来比较一下吧
Oh, really? Ok, let's compare, shall we?
现在说"好吗"是不是太晚了
Oh, it's so late for "shall we?"
我去过公园骑马吗?
Do I go horseback riding in the park, hmm?
我在新学院上过课吗?
Do I take classes at The New School?
不会      不会
No.        No.
太不公平了
This is so unfair
她拥有我想要的一切 而且不用应付我妈
She's got everything I want, and she doesn't have my mother.
乔伊帕帕尼如何?
How about Joey Paponi?
不行 太有种族意味了
No, still too ethnic.
我的经纪人认为我要取中立一点的名字
My agent thinks I should have a name that's more neutral.
乔伊瑞士?
Joey Switzerland?
而且我想叫乔 乔伊听起来好像我只有
Plus you know, I think it should be Joe. You know Joey makes me sound like I'm
这么大而已
this big.
但我并不是!
Which I'm not!
乔 乔 乔 斯大林?
Joe. Joe. Joe...Stalin?
斯大林
Stalin.
斯大林 我听过那个名字吗? 好耳熟
Stalin, do I know that name? That sounds familiar.
我没印象
Well, it does not ring a bell with me.
乔 斯大林
Joe Stalin.
还挺不错的
You know, that's pretty good.
还可以试试乔瑟夫
You might want to try Joseph.
乔瑟夫 斯大林!
Joseph Stalin!
大家一定会记得!      当然!
I think you'd remember that!        Oh, yes!
"别了 鸟儿" 由乔瑟夫斯大林主演
Bye Bye Birdie, starring Joseph Stalin.
乔瑟夫斯大林是"屋顶上的提琴手"
Joseph Stalin is the Fiddler on the Roof.
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hey.
嗨
Hi.
我是摩妮卡盖勒
Hi. Uh, yes, this is Monica Geller.
我想我有在你们那儿上课 我想知道是哪些课
Urn, I believe I'm taking some classes with you, and I was wondering what they were.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
好 太好了
All right, great.
好 谢谢了
Great. Thanks a lot.
我要去上踢踏舞课了
I'm going to tap class.
这样你就可以和偷了你信用的人一起跳舞吗?
What, what, so that you can dance with the woman that stole your credit card?
这个女人偷了我的人生 我应该知道她是谁
This woman's got my life. I should get to see who she is.
那就去邮局啊! 我确定她的照片会公布的
Go to the post office! I'm sure her picture's up!
摩妮卡 你有点失控了
Ok, Monica, you know you're kind of losing it here.
这已经变成怪异的执迷
I mean, this is really becoming like a weird obsession thing.
这太疯狂了
This is madness. It's madness, I tell you.
上帝保佑 摩妮卡别这么做
For the love of God, Monica, don't do it!
谢谢
Thank you.
你们怎么想?
What do you think?
想很多事情
Lots of things.
你觉得她是哪一个?
Which one do you think she is?
有什么需要我帮忙的么?      不用了 谢谢
May I help you?        Oh. no, thanks.
我们只是来参观的
We're just here to observe.
舞蹈课不是用来参观的 舞蹈课是来跳舞的
You don't observe a dance class. You dance a dance class!
那儿有鞋
Spare shoes are over there.
她什么意思?
What does she mean?
我想她是说"舞蹈课..."
I think she means, "You dance..."
是用来跳的!
a dance class!"
来吧!
Come on, come on, come on!
真的吗?
Really?
嘿 你有看到我的分身吗?
Hey, do you see anybody you think could be me?
各位 上次下课后有人留下空的优格瓶
People, last time there were empty yogurt containers lying around after class.
不要再发生这种事了!
Let's not have that happen again!
她可以当你的分身
She could be you.
开始吧
Let's get started.
五 六 五六七八
Five six. Five, six, seven, eight.
我完全不会!
Okay, I'm not getting this!
我完全融入!
I'm totally getting it!
你不会觉得自己有时毫无协调感么?
Do you ever just feel like sometimes you're just so unbelievably uncoordinated?
怎么了? 他们踢的时候你跟着踢就是了
What? You just click when they click.
好了 现在每个人找个舞伴
All right, people. Now everyone grab a partner
好吧 我死去的妈妈说就是你 我和瑞秋
All right. And my dead mother said you are it! I'm with Rachel.
太好了 体育课的旧事又重演了
Great. It's gym class all over again.
没关系 你可以来前面和我跳舞
That's all right. You can come up to the front and dance with me.
我还不如脱掉衣服做个恶梦算了?
Why don't I just take off my clothes and have a nightmare?
没关系 我来了! 很抱歉我迟到了
It's okay, it's okay! I'm here, I'm here. I'm so sorry I'm late.
好 我到了
Okay, here I am.
这位紧张的新人是谁?
So who's the new tense girl?
她是你的舞伴
She's your partner
嗨 我是摩妮卡
Hi, I'm Monica.
摩妮卡
Monica.
嗨 我是摩娜娜
Hi,I'm Mon
娜娜
Nana.
摩娜娜?      是的
Mon Nana?        Yeah.
是荷兰语
It's Dutch.
开玩笑吧 我在阿姆斯特丹待了三年
You're kidding. I spent three years in Amsterdam.
我是宾州的荷兰人
Urn, Pennsylvania Dutch.
要跳舞了!
And we're dancing!
五 六 七 八
Five, six, seven, eight.
嗨
Hi.
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hey.
你去哪了?      我刚从兽医那儿回来
Where have you been?        I just got back from the vet.
她不会叫你戴那些塑胶套吧?
She's not gonna make you wear a big plastic cone, is she?
她说马赛尔乱性不是暂时的
She says Marcel's humping thing is not a phase.
显然他已经性成熟了
Apparently, he's reached sexual maturity.
嘿 他比你还快诶!
Hey, he beat you!
她说他会越来越暴力 侵略性越来越强
She says as time goes on, he's gonna start getting aggressive and violent.
什么意思?
So what does this mean?
我得放弃他
I'm gonna have to give him up.
我不相信 罗斯 这太扯了!
I can't believe it. Ross, this sucks!
我不懂 你才刚养它 它怎么可能已经成年了?
I don't get it. I mean, you just got him. How could he be an adult already?
我知道 前一天它还是这么小的东西
I know I know. I mean, one day he's this little thing
不知不觉中就变成
and before you know it, he's this little thing
紧抓我的腿不放的小东西
I can't get off my leg.
没有办法能留下他吗?
Isn't there any way you can keep him?
没有
No. No.
兽医说除非有个地方能让他通过正常途径
The vet said that unless he's in a place where he has regular access
获得猴爱
to some monkey loving
否则他会越来越残暴
he's just gonna get vicious.
我得把他送到动物园
I just gotta get him into a zoo.
要怎么把猴子送到动物园?      我知道!
How do you get a monkey into a zoo?        I know that one!
不 那是教皇进入福斯汽车
No, that's popes into a Volkswagen.
我们申请了很多动物园 首选是州立动物园
We're applying to a lot of them. Naturally our first choice would be one of the bigger state zoos.
像是圣地亚哥
You know, like. uh, San Diego.
对吧?
Right?
但那可能是遥不可及的梦想 因为他来自州外
But that may just be a pipe dream, because, you know, he's out of state.
我的兽医在迈阿密有认识人 所以那儿有可能
My vet knows someone at Miami, so that's a possibility.
但那里离海滩只有两条街 肯定是个派对动物园
But that's two blocks away from the beach. I mean, it's a total party zoo.
嗨
Hey.
嗨      我们找到那个女生了!
Hi.        We found the girl!
什么?      你们报警了吗?
What?        Did you call the cops?
没 我们请她吃午餐
Nope. We took her to lunch.
你们自己的"自治正义"
Ah. Your own brand of vigilante justice.
你疯了吗?这个女人偷了你的东西!
Are you insane? This woman stole from you!
她偷东西 是小偷啊!
She stole! She's a stealer!
跟她相处十分钟 之后你就会把这些全忘了
You know what? After you're with this woman for like, 10 minutes, you forget all that.
她真的是个奇女子
I mean, she's this astounding person
振奋人心!
with this amazing spirit!
可能是从啦啦队员那里偷来的!
Yeah, which she probably stole from some cheerleader!
把帽子脱掉      福斯车里的教皇!
Take off their hats.        Popes in a Volkswagen!
我喜欢那个笑话
I love that joke.
不可能! 你不可能这么做!      摩娜娜很勇敢
No way! No way did you do this!        Monana was very brave.
这太疯狂了
It was so wild.
我们跟他们说 我们是615号房的冈氏姐妹
We told them we were the Gunnersons in room 615...
结果波士顿的塞尔蒂克队已经包下整个六楼!
only to find out the Boston Celtics had taken over the entire sixth floor!
当他们发现我们很矮而且有胸部后
So when they caught on to the fact that we're, you know, short and have breasts
他们把我们轰出去 我被饭店赶出去 我!
They threw us out. I was thrown out of a hotel! Me!
好样的 摩娜娜!
Go, Monana!
不是只有你们活在梦中
Well, you ladies are not the only ones living the dream.
我得去为我不认识的人倒咖啡了 不用等我
I get to go pour coffee for people I don'tknow. Don't wait up.
噢 还有一件事
Oh, by the way
我们明天要去参加百老汇的试镜
Tomorrow we're auditioning for a Broadway show.
什么?
Excuse me?
"猫"有一个缺额
There's an open call for Cats.
我想我们可以去 演唱"回忆"
I'm thinking we go down there, sing "Memories"
完全把自己当成傻子 你觉得怎样?
and make complete fools of ourselves. What do you say?
不 不 不
No no, no.
记得你身边的人是谁
Remember who you're dealing with here. Ha.
我不像你 我甚至不能站在踢踏舞教室前面
I mean, I'm not like you. I can't even stand in front of a tap class.
那可能是因为你有阿米许的背景
That's just probably because of your Amish background.
什么?      你是宾州的荷兰人 对吧?
What?        Well, you're Pennsylvania Dutch, right?
对的
Right.
直到我买了吹风机 就被逐出村里
Till I bought a blow dryer Then I was shunned.
我以前就跟你一样
I used to be just like you.
然后有一天 我看了一部改变我一生的电影
And then one day, I saw a movie that changed my life.
你看过"死亡诗社"吗?
Did you ever see Dead Poets Society?
我觉得那部电影超级
I thought that movie was so incredibly
无聊!
boring!
最后那个孩子
I mean, that thing at the end where the kid
自杀只是因为不能参加话剧演出?
kills himself because he can't be in the play?
那是在干什么?
What was that?
孩子 等一年 离开家 去社区话剧团
It's like, "Kid, wait a year. Leave home, do some community theater!"
我走出戏院后 心想
I walked out of there, and I thought
"我浪费了永远拿不回来的两小时人生"
"Now, that's two hours of my life that I'm never getting back!"
那个想法震撼了我 从此我及时行乐
And that thought scared me more than all the other crap I was afraid to do.
哇奥
Wow.
那我绝对不推荐你看"窈窕奶爸"
Then I would definitely not recommend Mrs. Doubtfire.
天啊
Oh. God.
我们进不了斯克兰顿
We didn't get into Scranton.
那是我们的保底动物园
That was our safety zoo.
他们连狗和牛都收
They take, like, dogs and cows.
看吧
See?
我不知道是我还是他比较难受
I don't know who this is harder on, me or him.
我想是那张椅子最难受
I'd say that chair's taking the brunt of it.
马赛尔 马赛尔
Marcel. Marcel.
马赛尔 不要弄了
Marcel. No.
好孩子!
Good boy!
看到了吗?怎么可能没人要他?
See? How can nobody want him?
会有人要的
Somebody will.
你们知道 已经有个乔瑟夫斯大林了吗?
You know there already is a Joseph Stalin?
你在开玩笑吧!
You're kidding!
显然他是个俄国独裁者 屠杀过很多人
Apparently, he was this Russian dictator who slaughtered all these people!
你怎么会不知道!      你想我该知道的
You'd think you would've known that!        You know you'd think I would've.
菲比 你觉得什么艺名适合我?
Phoebe, what do you think a good stage name for me would be?
火焰男孩!
Flame Boy!
你的动物园在哪里?
Where exactly is your zoo?
就技术上而言 它不能算是动物园
Well, it's technically not a zoo per se.
它比较像是互动的野生体验
It's, uh, more of an interactive wildlife experience.
让我问问你几个问题 他叫马赛尔 对吧?
Let me ask you some questions about, is it, uh, Marcel?
对      对
Yes.        Yes. Uh...
他会和其他动物打架吗?
Does he, uh, fight with other animals?
不 他非常温顺
No, no. He's very docile.
即使被逼到角落去呢?
Hmm. Even if he were cornered?
嗯 我不太清楚 为什么问这个?
Well, I don't know. Why?
他掌控小东西的能力为何?
Urn, how is he at handling small objects?
他可以握住香蕉 如果你是这个意思的话
He can hold a banana, if that's what you mean.
铁槌或小刀呢?
What about a hammer or a small blade?
他为什么会需要小刀?
Why, why, why would he need a blade?
如果他得面对猎豹或有角的动物
If he's up against a jungle cat or an animal with horns
总得给他点东西自我防卫吧
you've got to give the little guy something.
否则就太残忍了!
Otherwise it's just cruel!
他能去圣地亚哥了!
He got into San Diego!
什么?      对
What?        Yeah.
我们散步回来后 电话响了
We were coming back from our walking, and the phone was ringing
他进了!      他进了?
He's in!        He's in? Ah!
你听到了吗 马赛尔?
Did you hear that, Marcel?
是圣地亚哥! 圣地亚哥! 太棒了!
San Diego! San Diego! Yeah!
你正在犯下大错 圣地亚哥是不错
You're making a big mistake here. I mean, San Diego's well and good...
但如果你把他交给我 我会训练他对抗瞎眼的兔子
but if you give him to me, I'll start him against a blind rabbit
还给你百分之二十的门票收入
and give you 20 percent of the gate.
哟吼
Yoho!
你去哪儿了?
Where the hell've you been?
摩妮卡和我刚跑去参加大使馆派对
Monica and I just crashed an embassy party.
你喝醉了吗?
Are you drunk?
才没有!
No!
我在说谎
I'm lying.
我非常醉了!
I am so drunk!
天啊!
Oh, God!
太好了 摩妮卡 你该打个电话回来的
Ugh. Great. Monica, you know what? You could have called.
我一直在家里担心你
I've been up here.I've been worried...
摩妮卡
Monica
摩妮卡?
Monica?
水太棒了!
Water rules!
是的 没错
Yes. Yes it does.
餐厅今天又打电话来了
Ok, look. The restaurant called again today.
他们想知道你还去不去上班
They want to know if you're gonna be showing up for work.
不!
Nope!
我今天要去看大苹果马戏团
I'm going to the Big Apple Circus today.
摩妮卡 你在干嘛? 你会失去工作 你不是这样的
Ok, Monica. What are you doing? You're gonna lose your job. This is not you!
不 这就是我!
No, it is me!
我不只是那种需要拍松枕头
I'm not just the person who needs to fluff the pillows
帐单一来就立刻缴钱的人
and pay the bills as soon as they come in!
我跟她在一起时 我就超越了那种人!
You know, when I'm with her, I'm so much more than that!
我是
I'm
我是摩娜娜!
I'm Monana!
喂?
Ahem, hello?
她在 请稍等
Yes, she is. Hold on a second, please.
摩娜娜 找你的
Ahem, Monana, it's for you.
信用卡公司打来的
The credit card people.
喂?
Hello?
是
Yes?
天啊!
Oh, my God!
谢了
Thanks.
怎么了?
What?
他们逮捕摩妮卡了
They've arrested Monica.
嗨      嘿
Hi.        Hey.
你还好吗?
How are you?
还可以 幸好我喜欢蓝色
I'm not too bad. Fortunately, blue's my color.
你怎么知道我在这里的?
How did you know I was here?
因为
Because
我是摩妮卡盖勒
I'm Monica Geller.
你之前用的是我的信用卡
It was my credit card you were using.
真是没想到
That I was not expecting.
我想让你知道报案的人不是我
I want you to know, it wasn't me who turn you in.
哦
Oh.
谢了      不 我要谢谢你
Thanks.        No, thank you.
你带给我太多东西了
You have given me so much.
如果不是你我永远无法
If it wasn't for you, I'd never have gotten
在冬花园剧院演唱"回忆"
to sing Memories on the stage at the Winter Garden Theater.
其实你只开口唱了"回"而已
Actually, you only got to sing "Memo"
我不敢相信你在这里 没有你我该怎么办?
I can't believe you're in here. What am I gonna do without you?
谁跟我混进大使馆宴会?
Who's gonna crash the embassy parties with me?
谁带我去看大苹果马戏团?
Who's gonna take me to the Big Apple Circus?
摩妮卡 我从在25个人面前尿尿开始一天的生活
Monica, I started my day by peeing in front of 25 other women
你却担心谁带你去看大苹果马戏团?
and you're worried about who's gonna take you to the Big Apple Circus?
也不是担心 我只是纳闷而已
Well, not worried, you know, just wondering.
没什么好纳闷的 摩妮卡
There's nothing to wonder about, Monica.
你回去过以前的生活 因为那才是真正的你
You're gonna go back to being exactly who you were because that's who you are.
那不必要      那很必要
Not necessarily.         Yes necessarily.
我不知道是为什么 或许和你是阿米许人有关
I mean I don't know what it is. Maybe it's the Amish thing.
我其实不是阿米许人
Urn, I'm not actually Amish.
真的吗? 那你为何那么像?
Really? Then why are you like that?
站在门边的那个 要不要加入?
You by the door, in or out?
要!
In!
后面的那个 你全都跳错了!
You in the back, you're getting it all wrong!
至少我在跳
At least I'm doing it!
这是飞往圣地亚哥67航班的最后登机通知
This is the final boarding call for Flight 67 to San Diego
登机门为42A
boarding at Gate 42A.
再见了 小猴子
Okay, goodbye, little monkey guy.
我给你写了一首诗
I wrote you this poem.
但是上了飞机才能吃
Okay, but don't eat it till you get on the plane.
谢谢你 菲比阿姨
Thank you, Aunt Phoebe.
好 再见了 好小子
Okay, bye, champ.
我知道圣地亚哥有很多美眉
Now I know there's gonna be a lot of babes in San Diego
但是记得 要学的事情还很多
but remember, there's also a lot to learn.
罗斯 我不知道该说些什么 他是只猴子
I don't know what to say, Ross. Uh, it's a monkey.
说出心里的感受就行了 乔伊
Just say what you feel. Joey.
马赛尔 我饿了
Marcel, I'm hungry.
那很好啊
That was good.
马赛尔 这是给你的
Marcel, this is for you.
这是 你知道 这是给你
It's, uh, just, you know, something to, um...
在飞机上有事情做的
do on the plane.
如果你们不介意的话 我想跟他独处一下
If you guys don't mind, I'd like to take a moment, just me and him.
当然      当然可以      没问题
Sure.        Of course.        Absolutely.
马赛尔 到这儿来 这儿
Marcel, come here. Come here.
来吧
Come here.
兄弟
Well, buddy...
就这样了
this is it.
我想说几件事
There's just a couple of things I want to say.
我会很想你的
I'm really gonna miss you.
我永远不会忘记你
You know? And I'm never gonna forget about you.
你
You've
对我而言不只是只宠物
been more than just a pet to me.
你更像是
You've been more like a... Okay.
马赛尔 你
Marcel, would you?
马赛尔 你可以不要弄我的腿吗?
Marcel would you leave my leg alone
你能暂时不要乱来吗? 马赛?
Would you just stop humping me for two seconds? Marc...Would you?
好吧 麻烦把他带走吧 带走
Okay, would you just take him away? Just take him.
哦 希望我是你手上的手套
0h! that I were a glove upon that hand
这样就能抚模你的脸颊
that I might touch thy cheek.
行了 谢谢
That's fine. Thank you.
下一位
Next.
嗨 我来试演马丘修的角色
Hi. Uh, I'll be reading for the role of Mercutio.
名字?      豪顿 麦葛洛尼(Holding My Growing)
Name?        Holden McGroin.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧